prowrestling.net 2019-11-02

# Our Privacy Policy at ProWrestling.net - Pro Wrestling Dot Net

**Last updated: May 1, 2016**

Last Row Media LLC operates http://www.prowrestling.net (“ProWrestling.net”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of ProWrestling.net.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving ProWrestling.net. By usingProWrestling.net, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”).

**Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this information.

**Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing, or promotional materials and other information that you provide to us.

* * *

The new edition of the Pro Wrestling Boom Podcast with Jason Powell and guest Court Bauer, who discusses MLW Saturday Night SuperFight, his mindset just days before the company's first pay-per-view, the $19.99 price point, future PPV possibilities, the free pre-show, former WWE and Lucha Underground creative force Chris DeJoseph joining the MLW staff, and more...
